http://www.acadiarealty.com/privacy

CompanyPropertiesInvestorsAcquisitionsSustainabilityHuman CapitalContact
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
LAST UPDATED:
October 2014
This privacy statement describes our online privacy practices and
explains the choices you have about the way your information is
collected and used from this site.
Contacts at Acadia Realty Trust
If you have questions or concerns about your privacy when using this web site, please contact us by e-mail at privacy@acadiarealty.com, or via first class mail at:
Acadia Realty Trust
411 Theodore Fremd Ave
Suite 300
Rye, NY 10580
Personal Information
We do not collect personally identifying information about you on
this site unless you voluntarily submit it by registering or sending us a
message. There may be certain services or areas of this web site where
we will ask that you register and provide us with helpful information
about you and/or your company. This information may include information
about you and your company such as your name, title, company, address,
telephone number, email address, interests and other similar types of
information. You can access our web site home page and browse our sites
without disclosing your personal data.
Our web servers may use internet technology to collect information
that relates to your use of this web site, such as what browser you are
using or the domain name from which you entered the site. If we collect
this information, it is aggregated to measure critical data such as the
number of site visits, page views, average visiting time and other
statistics about visits to particular sites. It is not associated with
any personally identifying information. You may not be aware when this
information is being collected. We typically use such information to
improve the administration of our system and to identify needed
improvements to our web sites.
Use of Your Information
We use the information you provide:
to respond to your inquiries or service requests;
to notify you of property availabilities and other offerings;
to update you regarding your building or center if you are a tenant;
to conduct research; and/or
to contact you.
Except for the purposes stated in this policy, we will not use your
personally identifying information without your prior consent. We may
share your information with third parties to assist us with the uses
identified above, including without limitation our leasing broker and
building managers. We may also share your information with any third
party that purchases substantially all of our assets or business. We
will also share information we have collected with third parties as
required by law, regulation, legal process or governmental inquiry, or
to enforce any legal rights we may have against you.
Storing Information on Your Computer – “Cookies”
When you access this web site, we may store some information on your
computer that enables us to enhance navigation and functionality of our
web site, to verify your identity, to monitor usage statistics and to
personalize aspects of your experience on our web site. Such information
is sometimes called a “cookie.” We also may use cookies to let us know
how visitors are using our web site, so that we can improve the web site
and your experience on it. Most internet browsers allow you to erase
cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a
warning before a cookie is stored. Please be aware that if you reject
cookies, functionality on this web site may be limited.
Safeguarding Your Information
We intend to use reasonable safeguards to protect personally
identifying information we receive from unauthorized access or misuse.
Please understand, however, that no security precautions are perfect and
no guarantee is made against unauthorized access by third parties.
Children’s Privacy
We do not knowingly collect personally identifying information from
children under the age of 13 and we will delete that information if we
learn that it is from a child under the age of 13.
Links to Separate Web Sites
This web site may contain links to other web sites that may be
maintained by third parties. We are not responsible for the content or
privacy practices of such third-party web sites. We encourage you to
read and understand the privacy statements and related legal notices on
such other web sites.
Maintaining, Updating, Accessing and Removing Information
To access, review or update information you have submitted to us, or
if you wish to be removed from our web site database or notification
list, you can contact us at privacy@acadiarealy.com or by mail at:
Acadia Realty Trust
411 Theodore Fremd Ave
Suite 300
Rye, NY 10580
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to modify or supplement this Privacy Policy at
any time. Any personally identifying information submitted after such a
modification will be subject to the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.
For that reason, we suggest that you check the Privacy Policy
regularly.
Home
CompanyPropertiesPropertiesSearch PropertiesFull PortfolioView by AgentInvestorsNewsPresentations & EventsReportingQuarterly ResultsAnnual ReportsAnalyst CoverageSEC FilingsDividendsOfficersCorporate GovernanceBoard of TrusteesAnnual MeetingAcquisitionsSustainabilityEnvironmentalSocialGovernanceFull BrochureHuman CapitalHuman CapitalCulturePersonal DevelopmentInFocusCareersThe CampusContact
